ACTWU's General Executive Board (GEB) Records 5619/030
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- General Executive Board Minutes, Sept. 30 - Oct. 11, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  60th Anniversary at Miami Beach, FL
- General Executive Board Minutes, Jan. 37-30, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  San Juan, Puerto Rico
- General Executive Board Minutes, April 22-23, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- General Executive Board Minutes, Oct. 8-9, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- General Executive Board Minutes, Jan. 19-31, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- General Executive Board Minutes, March 16-17, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- General Executive Board Minutes, May 27-June 4, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  Washington D.C.
- General Executive Board Minutes, June 3-4, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- General Executive Board Minutes, July 23-24, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  Cherry Hill, NJ
- General Executive Board Minutes, Oct. 25-26, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- General Executive Board Minutes, March 1-7, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- General Executive Board Minutes, June 13-16, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- General Executive Board Minutes, Dec. 3-7, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  Palm Springs, CA
- General Executive Board Minutes, March 28-30, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- General Executive Board Minutes, June 12-16, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  Quebec City, Quebec
- General Executive Board Minutes, Aug. 15-16, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- General Executive Board Minutes, Sept. 18-29, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  Los Angeles, CA
- General Executive Board Minutes, Feb. 26-March 1, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- General Executive Board, March Resolutions, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- General Executive Board Minutes, May 30 - June 1, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- General Executive Board Minutes, Oct. 10-12, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  Hearing Officer's Reports, New York City
- 15 Union Square Corporation Minutes, Feb. 18, 1935 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Committee of Nine Minutes, Sept. 21, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Committee of Nine Minutes, Nov. 9-10, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Committee of Nine Minutes, Dec. 22, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Committee of Nine Minutes, Jan. 14, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Committee of Nine Minutes, Jan. 26, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Committee of Nine Minutes, March 29, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Committee of Nine Minutes, June 23-24, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Committee of Nine Minutes, Oct. 13, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- Committee of Nine Minutes, Dec. 7, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 39)
- Committee of Nine Minutes, March 10, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 40)
- Committee of Nine Minutes, June 7, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Committee of Nine Minutes, July 3, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Committee of Nine Minutes, August 10, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 43)
- Committee of Nine Minutes, August 31, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 44)
- Committee of Nine Minutes, Sept. 14, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 45)
- Committee of Nine Minutes, Sept. 25, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 46)
- Committee of Nine Minutes, Jan. 22, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 47)
- Committee of Nine Minutes, April 12, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 48)
- Committee of Nine Minutes, June 6, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 49)
- Committee of Nine Minutes, July 2, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Committee of Nine Minutes, Sept. 20, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 51)
- Committee of Nine Minutes, Dec. 4, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 52)
- Committee of Nine Minutes, Feb. 14, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 53)
- Committee of Nine Minutes, March 18, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 54)
- Committee of Nine Minutes, May 27, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 55)
- Committee of Nine Minutes, August 19, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 56)
- Committee of Nine Minutes, Nov. 30, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 57)
- Committee of Nine Minutes, Dec. 1, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 58)
- Committee of Nine Minutes, Dec. 9, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 59)
- Committee of Nine Minutes, Jan. 21, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 60)
- Committee of Nine Minutes, Jan. 4, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 61)
- Committee of Nine Minutes, Jan. 30, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 62)
- General Executive Board Meeting Reports, Sept. 5-8, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- General Executive Board Meeting Reports, May 15-19, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- General Executive Board Reports, November, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- General Executive Board Meeting Reports, Jan. 30 - Feb. 3, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- General Executive Board Reports, November, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- General Executive Board Meeting Reports, Sept. 14-16, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- General Executive Board Reports, April, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- General Executive Board Reports, February, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- General Executive Board Reports, October, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- General Executive Board Reports, May, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- General Executive Board Meeting Reports, Jan. 12-15, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- General Executive Board Meeting Reports, Oct. 20, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- General Executive Board Meeting Reports, July 10, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- General Executive Board Meeting Reports, March 14, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- General Executive Board Meeting Reports, Jan. 6, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- General Executive Board Meeting Reports, Oct. 18, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- General Executive Board Meeting Reports, Feb. 28, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- General Executive Board Reports, Dec. 20, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- General Executive Board Meeting Reports, July 25, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- General Executive Board Meeting Reports, August 21-28, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  Elections and Industry Reports
- General Executive Board Meeting Reports, Feb. 7-27, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- General Executive Board Report on Elections, Certifications and Agreements, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- General Executive Board Meeting Reports, Feb. 16-19, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- General Executive Board Meeting Reports, July 6-21, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- General Executive Board Meeting Reports, March 7-31, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- General Executive Board Meeting Reports, Nov. 5-22, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- General Executive Board Meeting Reports, July 7-22, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- General Executive Board Meeting Reports, Feb. 2-18, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- General Executive Board Report on Elections, Certifications and Agreements, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- General Executive Board Meeting Reports, Oct. 5-16, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- General Executive Board Meeting Reports, April 30-May6, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- General Executive Board Meeting Reports, Feb. 4-5, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- General Executive Board Meeting Reports, Feb. 4-8, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- General Executive Board Report on General Economic Conditions, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- General Executive Board Report on General Economic Conditions, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- General Executive Board Report on General Economic Conditions, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 36)
- General Executive Board Report on General Economic Conditions, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 37)
- General Executive Board Report on General Economic Conditions, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 38)
- General Executive Board Report on General Economic Conditions, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 39)
- General Executive Board Report on General Economic Conditions, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 40)
- General Executive Board Report on General Economic Conditions, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 41)
- General Executive Board Report on General Economic Conditions, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 42)
- General Executive Board Report on General Economic Conditions, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 43)
- General Executive Board Report on General Economic Conditions, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 44)
- General Executive Board Report on General Economic Conditions, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 45)
- General Executive Board Minutes, Feb. 25-29, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- General Executive Board Minutes, May 5, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- General Executive Board Minutes, August 26-27, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  Bushkill, PA
- General Executive Board Minutes, Hearing Committee Reports, August 26-27, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- General Executive Board Minutes, Oct. 19, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- General Executive Board Minutes, Jan. 7, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- General Executive Board Minutes, Feb. 23-27, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- General Executive Board Minutes, Hearing Officer Reports, Feb. 26-27, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  Charges against Frank Byers, Anna Blake and Susie Conley
- General Executive Board Minutes, April 14-15, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- General Executive Board Minutes, May 25-June 4, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  Detroit, MI
- General Executive Board Minutes, Oct. 26-28, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- General Executive Board Minutes, May 20-21, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- General Executive Board Minutes, July 27-30, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  Tarrytown, NY
- General Executive Board Minutes, March 8, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- General Executive Board Meeting Reports, March 8, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  Hearing Committee
- General Executive Board Meeting Reports, March 8, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  Hearing Officer's Report and Passed Resolution
- General Executive Board Minutes, Dec. 7-10, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- General Executive Board Minutes, Jan. 20-21, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- General Executive Board Minutes, April 11-15, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  Philadelphia, PA
- General Executive Board Minutes, Aug. 1-5, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- General Executive Board Minutes, Sept. 29-30, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  Hollywood, FL
- General Executive Board Minutes, March 5-8, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- General Executive Board Minutes, May 1-3, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- General Executive Board Minutes, June 4-6, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Hearing Officer's Report, Charges filed against Mary Woods, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  Local #1820, Ohio
- General Executive Board Minutes, Sept. 5-7, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  Montreal, Quebec
- Hearing Officer's Report, Appeal by Carol Wallitsch, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  Local #630, New Jersey
- Hearing Officer's Report, Appeal by Ann Sondelski, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  Local #958T, Illinois
- Hearing Officer's Report, Appeal by Kenneth Morgan, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Hearing Officer's Report, Charges filed by Members of Local #14T, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Hearing Officer's Report, Administratorship for Local #262-SW, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- General Executive Board Minutes, Oct. 31 - Nov. 1, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  Anaheim, CA
- Hearing Officer's Report, Charges filed against Manuel Rivera, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- General Executive Board, Charters Issued, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Hearing Officer's Report, Charges filed against Michael Feinstein, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  Local #2H
- Hearing Officer's Report, Charges filed against Wilfredo Larancuent, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Hearing Committee Report, Administratorship of the Cap Makers' Union Local #2H, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- General Executive Board Resolution, Administratorship of the Philadelphia Joint Board, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Interim Actions of the General Executive Board, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Hearing Officer's Report, Charges filed against Sharon Riffle, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  Local #1901, Ohio
- Hearing Committee Report, Charges filed against Bruce Dunton and Warwick Daniel, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  Local #317T, Virginia
- General Executive Board Resolution, Charges filed against Bruce Dunton and Warwick Daniel, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- General Executive Board Minutes, Jan. 9-10, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- General Executive Board, Charters, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Interim Actions of the General Executive Board, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- General Executive Board Resolutions, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- General Executive Board, Letters on Trusteeship of Western Ontario Joint Board, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Hearing Officer's Report, Appeal of Lionel Labonville, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  Local #183-SW, New Hampshire
- Hearing Officer's Report, Appeal by Shirley Weaver, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  Local #1598, New Jersey
- Hearing Officer's Report, Appeal by Robert Frankenfield, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  Local #1921, New Jersey
- Hearing Officer's Report, Appeal by Lorraine Seguin, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  Local #740, Ontario
- General Executive Board, Proposed Amendments to the Retirement Plan, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- General Executive Board Minutes, March 11-15, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- General Executive Board Minutes, July 29-August 2, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Hearing Officer's Report, Appeal by Luis Leandro, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  Local #110T, Connecticut
- Hearing Officer's Report, Appeal by Robert Hoyle, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  Local #939T, Connecticut
- Hearing Officer's Report, Charges filed by Manuel Rivera against Michael Feinstein and vice versa, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  Local #2H of the Cap Makers' Union
- Hearing Committee Report, Administratorship of the Cap Makers' Union Local #2H, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 34)
- General Executive Board Resolution, Charges against Michael Feinstein, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 35)
- General Executive Board, Reaffirmation of Administratorship of Local #2H, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 36)
- US District Court, Southern District of New York, Cap Makers Union Local #2H, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 37)
- Cap Makers' Union Local #2H, Letter to Manuel Rivera, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 38)
- ACTWU, Letters to Rivera and Feinstein, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 39)
- ACTWU, Letter to Feinstein concerning the Reaffirmation of the Administratorship of Local #2H, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 40)
- New England Regional Joint Board, Edward Clark letters to Feinstein and Rivera, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 41)
- ACTWU, additional charges against Michael Feinstein, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 42)
- Letter on Continued Administratorship of Local #2H, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 43)
- Hearing, Manuel Rivera, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 44)
- ACTWU, Letters concerning charges filed against Michael Feinstein, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 45)
- Local #2H, Dept of Labor and New York State Forms, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 46)
- Cap Makers' Union Local #2H, Letters to Samuel Schechter, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 47)
- United States District Court, Southern District Court of New York, Cap Makers' Union Local #2H, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  Michael Feinstein v. Jack Sheinkman
- ACTWU, Constitution Sections 13-16, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 49)
- Cap Makers' Union Local #2H, Administratorship, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 50)
- Local #2H, Letters from Michael Feinstein, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 51)
- Cap Makers' Union Local #2H, Letter Exchange, Wilfredo Larancuent, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 52)
- Local #2H and Empire State Cloth Hat & Cap Manufacturers Association, 1984-1987 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  Collective Bargaining Agreement
- Cap Makers' Union Local #2H, Letter Exchange, Manufacturers, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 54)
- Cap Makers' Union Local #2H, Work Permit Cards, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 55)
- Daily Shop Visit Summary Reports, Michael Feinstein, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 56)
- Cap Makers' Union Local #2H, Weekly Activities Reports, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 57)
- Local #2H, Staff Meeting, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 58)
- Cap Makers' Union Local #2H, Reports from Workers, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 59)
- Cap Makers' Union Local #2H, Michael Feinstein's Reports, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 60)
- General Executive Board Minutes, January 13-16, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 61)
- General Executive Board Minutes, May 17-20, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 62)
- General Executive Board, ACTWU Retirement Plan, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 63)
- General Executive Board, Amalgamated Staff Retirement Plan, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 64)
- General Executive Board Minutes, July 14-17, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 65)
  Rye Brook, NY
- General Executive Board Minutes, Oct. 28-30, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 66)
- General Executive Board, Reports on Elections, Certifications and Agreements, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- General Executive Board, Industry Reports, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  December
- General Executive Board, Elections, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- General Executive Board, Industry Reports, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  July
- General Executive Board, Elections, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- General Executive Board, Industry Reports, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  February
- General Executive Board, Elections, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- General Executive Board, Industry Reports, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  October
- General Executive Board, Elections, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- General Executive Board, Industry Reports, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  May
- General Executive Board, Elections, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- General Executive Board, Industry Reports, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- General Executive Board, Elections, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- General Executive Board, Elections and Industry Reports, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  August
- General Executive Board, Industry Reports, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- General Executive Board, Elections, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- General Executive Board, Industry Reports, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- General Executive Board, Elections, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- General Executive Board, General Economic Conditions, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  April
- General Executive Board, General Economic Conditions, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- General Executive Board, General Economic Conditions, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  January
- General Executive Board, General Economic Conditions, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- General Executive Board, General Economic Conditions, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- General Executive Board, General Economic Conditions, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- General Executive Board, General Economic Conditions, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- General Executive Board, General Economic Conditions, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- General Executive Board, General Economic Conditions, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  March
- General Executive Board, General Economic Conditions, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 28)
- General Executive Board, General Economic Conditions, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  September
- General Executive Board, General Economic Conditions, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 30)
- General Executive Board, General Economic Conditions, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 31)
- General Executive Board, General Economic Conditions, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 32)
- General Executive Board, General Economic Conditions, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 33)
- General Executive Board, General Economic Conditions, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  November
- General Executive Board, General Economic Conditions, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 35)
- General Executive Board, General Economic Conditions, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 36)
- General Executive Board, General Economic Conditions, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 37)
- General Executive Board, General Economic Conditions, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 38)
- General Executive Board, General Economic Conditions, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 39)
- General Executive Board, General Economic Conditions, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 40)
- General Executive Board, General Economic Conditions, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 41)
- General Executive Board, General Economic Conditions, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 42)
- General Executive Board, General Economic Conditions, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 43)
- General Executive Board, General Economic Conditions, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 44)
- General Executive Board, General Economic Conditions, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 45)
- General Executive Board, General Economic Conditions, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  June
- General Executive Board, General Economic Conditions, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 47)
- General Executive Board, General Economic Conditions, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 48)
- General Executive Board, General Economic Conditions, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 49)
- General Executive Board, Reports on Election, Recognitions and First Agreements, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- General Executive Board, Reports on Elections, Recognitions and Agreements, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- General Executive Board, Reports on Male Apparel, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- General Executive Board, Reports on Textile, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- General Executive Board, Reports on Nonrubber Footwear, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- General Executive Board, Elections, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- General Executive Board, Reports on Male Apparel, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- General Executive Board, Reports on Textile, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- General Executive Board, Reports on Nonrubber Footwear, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- General Executive Board, Elections, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- General Executive Board, Reports on Male Apparel, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- General Executive Board, Reports on Textile, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- General Executive Board, Reports on Nonrubber Footwear, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- General Executive Board, Elections, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- General Executive Board, Reports on Male Apparel, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- General Executive Board, Reports on Textile, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- General Executive Board, Reports on Nonrubber Footwear, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- General Executive Board, Elections, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- General Executive Board, Reports on Male Apparel, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- General Executive Board, Reports on Textile, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- General Executive Board, Reports on Nonrubber Footwear, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- General Executive Board, Elections, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- General Executive Board, Reports on Male Apparel, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- General Executive Board, Reports on Textile, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- General Executive Board, Reports on Nonrubber Footwear, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- General Executive Board, Elections, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 26)
- General Executive Board, Reports on Male Apparel, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 27)
- General Executive Board, Reports on Textile, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 28)
- General Executive Board, Reports on Nonrubber Footwear, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 29)
- General Executive Board, Elections, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 30)
- General Executive Board, Reports on Male Apparel, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 31)
- General Executive Board, Reports on Textile, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 32)
- General Executive Board, Reports on Nonrubber Footwear, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 33)
- General Executive Board, Elections, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 34)
- General Executive Board, Industry Reports, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 35)
- General Executive Board, Industry Reports, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 36)
- General Executive Board, Elections, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 37)
- General Executive Board, Industry Reports, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 38)
- General Executive Board, Elections, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 39)
- General Executive Board, Industry Reports, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 40)
- General Executive Board, Elections, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 41)
- General Executive Board, Industry Reports, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 42)
- General Executive Board, Elections, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 43)
- Bureau of Labor Statistics, Industrial Survey in Selected Industries, 1919 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  Bulletin of the US Bureau of Labor Statistics No. 265
- Federal Works Agency First Annual Report, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Department of Labor, Walsh-Healey Public Contracts Act, 1936 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  Matter of the prevailing minimum wages in the men's work garment industry as provided by Section 1(b) of Public Act No. 846, 74th Congress
- Department of Labor, Hearing before the Sub-Committees of Apparel Industry Committee, 1939 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  Men's Neckwear, Handbags and Handkerchiefs
- Department of Labor, Minimum Wage in the Glove Industry, 1942 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  Minimum Wage of Forty Cents an Hour will not Curtail Employment, to Industry Committee No. 40
- Department of Labor, Woolen Trouser Industry, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  Hearing on Amendment of the Prevailing Wage Determination for the Woolen Trouser Industry
- Department of Labor, Cotton Garment and Allied Industries pg. 1-100, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  Hearing on Amendment of the Prevailing Minimum Wage Determination for the Cotton Garment and Allied Industries
- Department of Labor, Cotton Garment and Allied Industries pg. 101-200, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Department of Labor, Cotton Garment and Allied Industries pg. 201-300, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Department of Labor, Employment Regulations on Learners pg. 1-100, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 10)